Finding Aid for News and Information Services (University of Michigan) photograph series D (faculty and staff portraits), 1946-2006
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Series D, Faculty and Staff Portraits
  - W
    - Wilder, Raymond L., Mathematics, 1958, 1966, 1972 (Box 15)
    - Wile, Udo J., 1947 (Box 15)
    - Wilensky, Harold L., Sociology, 1961, 1959 (Box 15)
    - Wiley, John H., Speech, 1969, 1978, 1975 (Box 15)
    - Wilfong, Arch., Naval Science, 1964 (Box 15)
    - Wilhelm, Ross, Business Economics, 1966, 1976 (Box 15)
    - Wilhelm, Rowena M., Institute of Human Adjustment, 1982, 1970 (Box 15)
    - Wilkes, David, Data Management Computer Systems, 1983 (Box 15)
    - Wilkes, James, Chemical Engineering, 1963, 1961, 1978, 1970 (Box 15)
    - Wilkins, John A., Extension Service, 1963, 1971, 1967 (Box 15)
      (nb 1003-1005)
    - Wilkinson, Warren, Continuing Engin. Program, 1971 (Box 15)
    - Willard, Hobart H., Chemistry, 1948, 1950 (Box 15)
    - Willcox, William, History, 1963 (Box 15)
    - Willey, Norman L., 1948 (Box 15)
    - Williams, Brymer, Chemical and Metallurgical Engineering, 1960, 1978, 1974 (Box 15)
    - Williams, Donald, English Language Institute, 1963 (Box 15)
    - Williams, Donald W., Music (Box 15)
    - Williams, Frank, University Relations; Strategic Planning, 1994 (Box 15)
    - Williams, Glen R., Alumni Association, 1964, 1973, 1978, 1971 (Box 15)
    - Williams, Karen, Library Sciences, 1982 (Box 15)
    - Williams, Laura, Education, 1975 (Box 15)
    - Williams, Lawrence K., Survey Research Center, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Williams, Marilyn J., Medical Information, 1978 (Box 15)
    - Williams, Melvin D., Anthropology, 1988 (Box 15)
    - Williams, Michelle, Music, 1985 (Box 15)
    - Williams, Ralph, English, 1992, 1986, 1991, 1974 (Box 15)
    - Williams, Robert F., Center for Chinese Studies, 1971 (Box 15)
    - Williams, Robert L., Education, 1960, 1948, 1949 (Box 15)
    - Williams, Robley, 1949 (Box 15)
      (na 2708-2711)
    - Williams, Virginia, Community Health Services, 1963 (Box 15)
    - Williams, William J., Electrical Engineering, 1964, 1977 (Box 15)
    - Willing, Jean, Real Estate Program, 1979 (Box 15)
    - Willis, Edgar, Speech, 1957, 1986, 1969, 1975 (Box 15)
    - Willmarth, William W., Aeronautical Engineering, 1960, 1973 (Box 15)
    - Willson, J. Robert (Box 15)
    - Wilson, Barbara, News Service (Box 15)
    - Wilson, Blenda (Box 15)
    - Wilson, Dean H., Institute for Science and Technology; Industrial Engineering, 1962, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Wilson, Diana, Oxford House, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Wilson, Frank N. (Box 15)
      (na 2705)
    - Wilson, Gayle, Admissions, 1964, 1957, 1954, 1967 (Box 15)
    - Wilson, George, Music, 1970 (Box 15)
    - Wilson, Hal, Alumni Association, 1964, 1978, 1971 (Box 15)
    - Wilson, Herbert (Box 15)
      (na 2706-2707)
    - Wilson, James T., Institute of Science and Technology; Geology, 1962, 1970, 1965, 1976 (Box 15)
    - Wilson, Linda (Box 15)
    - Wilson, Paul, Social Work, 1986 (Box 15)
    - Wilson, Richard C., Engineering, 1967, 1960, 1974 (Box 15)
    - Wilson, Robert, Correspondence Study, 1966, 1971 (Box 15)
      (nb 979-n983)
    - Wilson, Roselle, VP for Student Affairs (Box 15)
    - Wilson, Russell, Education, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Wilson, Virginia, Physical Therapy, 1964, 1958, 1964 (Box 15)
    - Wilt, Glenn A. Jr., School of Business Administration, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Wilt, Richard, Art, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Winans, Sarah, Anatomy, 1975 (Box 15)
    - Wineman, Alan, Applied Mechanics, 1975, 1964, 1991 (Box 15)
    - Winer, Ward, Mechanical Engineering, 1963, 1968 (Box 15)
    - Wing, Lisa, Hopwood Winner (Box 15)
    - Wingo, Max, Education, 1953 (Box 15)
    - Winkelman, Eugene I., Internal Medicine, 1961 (Box 15)
    - Winkelmann, John R., Museum of Zoology, 1962 (Box 15)
    - Winkels, Dale R., Slavic Languages and Literatures, 1961 (Box 15)
    - Winkler, James M., Surgery, 1963 (Box 15)
    - Winter, Charlotte C., Survey Research Center, 1958 (Box 15)
      (na 2701-2704)
    - Winter, David G., Psychology, 1996 (Box 15)
    - Winter, Kenton, Public Health Economics, 1963, 1956 (Box 15)
      (na 2693)
    - Wise, Kensall D., Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1979 (Box 15)
    - Wisler, Chester O., Hydraulic Engineering, 1950, 1960 (Box 15)
      (na 2690-2692)
    - Wisterberg, Martha, University Hospital, 1973 (Box 15)
    - Wit, Daniel, 1955 (Box 15)
      (na 2689)
    - Withey, Stephen B., Survey Research Center; Psychology, 1955 (Box 15)
    - Withrow, Norval E., Music, 1973 (Box 15)
    - Witke, Charles, Classical Studies, 1971 (Box 15)
    - Witt, Vicente M., Civil Engineering, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Witten, Winnie, Women's Gymnastics Coach, 1978 (Box 15)
    - Witter, John A., Etomology, 1978, 1973 (Box 15)
    - Wixom, Charles W., Information News Service, 1962, 1966 (Box 15)
    - Wixon, Karen, Education, 1986, 1995, 1983 (Box 15)
    - Wixson, Charles, Highway Safety, 1969 (Box 15)
    - Wohl, Milton, English Language Institute, 1965 (Box 15)
    - Wolf, Eric R., Anthropology, 1962 (Box 15)
    - Wolf, Karen, Student, 1990 (Box 15)
    - Wolf, Melvin H., English, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Wolf, R. Craig, Speech Communication and Theatre, 1974 (Box 15)
    - Wolfe, David L., Spanish, 1963 (Box 15)
    - Wolfe, Neil, Student, 1971 (Box 15)
    - Wolfenden, Elmer, English Language Institute, 1965 (Box 15)
    - Wolfson, Charles, Social Work, 1964 (Box 15)
    - Womack, Farris, VP and Chief Financial Officer, 1988 (Box 15)
    - Womer, Frank B., Education, 1957, 1969 (Box 15)
    - Wong, Helen, English Language Institute, 1954 (Box 15)
    - Wong, Henery, Chemical Engineering, 1985 (Box 15)
    - Wood, Arthur E., 1951 (Box 15)
    - Wood, Dorothy, 1967 (Box 15)
    - Wood, Gordon, History, 1967 (Box 15)
    - Wood, Harris, Naval Science, 1964 (Box 15)
    - Wood, James H., DSC, 1979 (Box 15)
    - Woodburne, Russell T., Anatomy and Postgraduate Medicine, 1948, 1958 (Box 15)
    - Woodford, John, News and Information Services, 1985 (Box 15)
    - Woodhead, Arthur E., Zoology, 1958 (Box 15)
    - Wooding, Edmund, Journalism, 1952, 1953, 1958, 1967 (Box 15)
    - Wooding, Peter, Student, 1963 (Box 15)
    - Woodman, Ernest A. H., Natural Resources, 1967 (Box 15)
    - Woodruff, Calvin, Nutrition, 1963 (Box 15)
    - Woods, Richard D., Civil Engineering, 1970 (Box 15)
    - Woodward, Alvalyn E., Zoology (Box 15)
    - Woodward, John, Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering, 1963, 1971 (Box 15)
    - Woodworth, G. Walter, Business Administration, 1959 (Box 15)
    - Woolery, Todd, Extension Service, 1967 (Box 15)
    - Woolley, Doug, Registrar, 1992 (Box 15)
    - Worden, Orien, 1969 (Box 15)
    - Work, Walter, 1967 (Box 15)
    - Wrangham, Richard, Anthropology, 1983 (Box 15)
    - Wright, Gavin, Economics, 1977 (Box 15)
    - Wright, Jesse, Math, ERI, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Wright, L. Hart, Law, 1949, 1958, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Wright, L. Hart, Law, 1978 (Box 15)
    - Wright, Paul William, Registrar, 1986 (Box 15)
    - Wright, Roger, Business Administration, 1966 (Box 15)
    - Wright, Susan, LSA, 1983 (Box 15)
    - Wrobleski, William, Business Administration, 1963, 1965 (Box 15)
    - Wrubel, David F., Hopwood, 1968 (Box 15)
    - Wu, Chung, Biological Chmistry; Internal Medicine, 1959 (Box 15)
    - Wulff, Yvonne L., University Library, 1990 (Box 15)
    - Wyatt, Frederick, Psychology, 1955, 1965 (Box 15)
    - Wyatt, Stanley, 1951 (Box 15)
      (na 2679-n2682)
    - Wylie, E. Benjamin, Civil Engineering, 1966, 1972 (Box 15)
    - Wyllie, Cleland B., University Relations, 1960, 1952 (Box 15)
  - Y
    - Yablonky, Ben, Journalism, 1975, 1960, 1961 (Box 15)
    - Yacomb, Journalism, 1955 (Box 15)
    - Yagle, Raymond A., Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering, 1977, 1959 (Box 15)
    - Yamagiwa, Joseph K., Far Eastern Languages and Literatures, 1962 (Box 15)
    - Yang, Chin T., Mechanical Engineering, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Yang, Wen-Jei, Mechanical Engineering, 1978, 1962 (Box 15)
    - Yates, Edward A., Engineering Mechanics, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Yates, Warren G., Southeast Asian Regional English Project, 1958 (Box 15)
    - Yeh, Chai, Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1971, 1983, 1961, 1978 (Box 15)
    - Yeh, Gregory, Materials Engineering, 1977 (Box 15)
    - Yellin, Seymour, Sociology, 1958 (Box 15)
      (na 2678)
    - Yentz, Arlene, Extension Service, 1972 (Box 15)
    - Yih, Chia-Shun, Applied Mechanics, 1978, 1973, 1960, 1965 (Box 15)
    - Yntema, Hessel E., Comparative Law, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Yocum, Charles, Biological Science, 1978 (Box 15)
    - Yocum, Paula, 1977 (Box 15)
    - Yoder, Sharon, State and Community Relations, 1976, 1979, 1973 (Box 15)
    - York, J. Louis, Chemical and Metallurgical Engineering, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Young, Edward, Geodesy and Surveying, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Young, Edwin H., Chemical and Metallurgical Engineering, 1960, 1974, 1979 (Box 15)
    - Young, John B., Pharmacy, 1970 (Box 15)
    - Young, John G., Mechanical Engineering, 1954, 1960, 1969 (Box 15)
    - Young, Raymond J., Higher Education, 1964, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Young, Richard E., Humanities; English, College of Engineering, 1974, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Young, Suzanne M., Student Prog. UAC, 1977, 1979 (Box 15)
    - Youngdahl, Paul, Mechanical Engineering, 1971, 1962 (Box 15)
    - Youtie, Herbert C., Papyrology, 1962, 1961 (Box 15)
    - Youtz, Philip N., Architecture and Design, 1958, 1968 (Box 15)
    - Youvan (Box 15)
    - Yu, Mirian, AAUW, 1971 (Box 15)
    - Yu, Tiong S., Electrical Engineering, 1962 (Box 15)
    - Yuill, Robert S., Geography, 1965 (Box 15)
  - Z
    - Zahner, Robert, Forestry, 1959, 1961 (Box 15)
    - Zald, Mayer N., Sociology, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Zamiska, Leonard W., Art, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Zand, Robert, Biophysics, 1977 (Box 15)
    - Zander, Alvin F., Center for Group Dynamics; Psychology; Education, 1971, 1962, 1955 (Box 15)
    - Zappen, James P., Humanities, 1980 (Box 15)
    - Zarafonetis, Chris J. D., Internal Medicine, 1961, 1950 (Box 15)
    - Zarrugh, Mohamed Y., Mechanical Engineering, 1978 (Box 15)
    - Zeff, Stephen A., Business Administration, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Zeigler, Bernard, Computer and Communication Sciences, 1972, 1969 (Box 15)
    - Zeigler, Earle F., Education (Box 15)
    - Zeisler, Karl F., Journalism, 1953, 1969 (Box 15)
    - Zeller, William J., Housing, 1995 (Box 15)
    - Zerman, Bill, 1952 (Box 15)
      (na 2948)
    - Zern, Richard D., Business Administration, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Ziff, Robert, Chemical Engineering, 1982 (Box 15)
    - Zimmerman, E. R., 1968 (Box 15)
    - Zimmerman, Floyd, Landscape Architecture, 1966 (Box 15)
    - Zimmerman, William (Box 15)
    - Zinn, Karl L., CRLT; Psychology, 1979, 1971, 1970, 1968 (Box 15)
    - Zinnes, Joseph, Psychology, 1959 (Box 15)
      (nb 976-978)
    - Zito, James M., English Language and Literature, 1964 (Box 15)
    - Zografi, George, Chemistry, 1968 (Box 15)
    - Zuck, Joyce, ELI, 1975 (Box 15)
    - Zuck, Louis, ELI, 1964 (Box 15)
    - Zuckerman, Howard, HSMP, 1987 (Box 15)
    - Zuidema, George, 1963 (Box 15)
    - Zumberge, James H., Geology, 1958, 1962 (Box 15)
    - Zweifel, Paul F., Nuclear Engineering, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Zwerk, Charles, Extension Service; Business Administration, 1962 (Box 15)
    - Zygert (Box 15)